Itadori, why is
his nose bleeding?
I smashed in his face.
But when?
At the start of the fight.
And did his hand touch you?
Mm-hmm.
My attacks aren't
going to work on him.
Huh? Wait, what?
But why not?
I'll explain it later
while I'm lecturing you.
It's either because, one:
his technique doesn't
work on Itadori.
Or two: there's some
reason he won't kill Itadori.
Either way, it's good for us.
However, I'll try to keep
him from moving around.
Then, once we've
both got an opening,
we'll shower him with blows.
We'll exorcise this
one, here and now.
Yeah!
I'll keep an eye
on Yuuji Itadori,
while I start by taking out
the Seven to Three sorcerer.
Hmmm.
I thought that would
be a good one to use.
But they both just dodged it
and then, they started
shaving away the weaker ends.
I guess it only
works on small fry.
Time to stop!
(roars)
(attack grunt)
Notice just before
he changes shape...
He stores cursed energy.
Right.
(laughs)
Even though I've
made myself smaller,
there's still some
danger of Yuuji Itadori
killing me in one blow.
He really is my natural enemy.
So I'll need to make him behave.
(vomiting)
Transfigured humans!
He still had a
stockpile of them?
Kill the short-haired brat, you!
Look, he's running from them!
I knew he couldn't kill humans!
(attack chittering, gibberish)
You wanna play?
Please kill me.
Please?
Next I should have
him attack you, sorcerer.
You think he'll cry then too?
He's a foolish brat who
can't reconcile reality
with his ideals.
You're wrong about that.
He's right in the process of
making that reconciliation.
If you want to
know what I think...
I'd say you're the fool.
(surprised laugh)
Did you kill those three?
Damn, they know my tricks now!
They know I change shape right
before the moment of impact.
(agony yell)
They're not giving me enough
time to create a substitute!
Ahh!
What fresh inspiration this is!
Is this...
Death?
(building laughter)
I bet I could do it now!
Domain Expansion!
Self-Embodiment of Perfection!
No!
Right now, I'm just so
grateful to you.
(opening theme music)
"Jujutsu Kaisen"
"Episode 13: Tomorrow"
(punching efforts, grunting)
Quit screwing around!
Why'd he seal Nanami
inside and not me?
What do I do?
What can I do?
Domain Expansion.
Within an innate domain
constructed from cursed energy,
the ultimate
technique becomes one
that's guaranteed
to hit its target.
It's the height of jujutsu
sorcery I could never reach.
Most likely, his
cursed technique
requires touching the target
with his palm in its base state,
in order to interfere
with the victim's soul.
However, in a domain
that guarantees a hit,
that would mean
that now, I'm literally...
In the palm of his hand.
Shit.
Jujutsu sorcerers are shit.
They have to be prepared
to sacrifice their
lives for others,
and occasionally force their
comrades to do so as well.
That's why I quit.
Though, ran away
is more like it.
[Bakery Girl] You really like
our ham and cheese, don't you?
Huh?
(laugh)
You always order
the same sandwich.
Oh, uh, yeah.
They stopped selling it at
my local convenience store.
Ours is probably better
than theirs anyway.
Yeah, well you are a bakery.
Hey, give us a little credit!
See you next time!
A fly head.
Leaving it alone
won't hurt anything.
It'd be a bigger
pain to deal with it
and have her think I'm
some weird medium.
Hello, everybody!
Listen up!
Make those sales!
When people trust
us with their money,
they're trusting
us with their lives.
So it goes without saying
that we have to balance
the pursuit of profit
against the risks.
There's no need to do
anything special at the start.
Just be sincere
with the clients.
Mm-hmm.
Try never to forget that.
[New Guy] Right!
Nanami...
Don't be so damned
serious all the time,
you're freaking out the virgin.
New boy, what you
need to think about first
is the company's profits!
If we don't profit then
neither does the client!
Even when we con them
into buying shit stocks
with no growth potential?
Of course!
It's a well-deserved payment
given the fact that
we spend our days
staring at the markets
around the clock!
Nanami, this is your
second year, right?
You're clever, let
yourself run wild, okay!
I expect great things from you!
I'm a person who's never
gotten the concept of
"reason for living" or
"something worth doing."
I figure I'll just
earn enough money
by the time I'm 30 or 40,
to enjoy the rest
of my aimless life
in some country with
a low cost of living.
It's been four years
since I left the school.
Now, whether I'm
awake or asleep,
all I think about is money.
Curses and other people
have nothing to do with me,
as long I have money.
Money.
Money, money.
As long as I have money.
Are you all right?
I mean are you
getting enough sleep?
What about you?
You look like you've
been carrying around
some serious stress.
Ha, you can tell that huh?
Lately I feel like there's
this weight on my shoulder.
I haven't been
sleeping well, either.
[Nanami] Essentially my job--
Hm?
Is to take money
from wealthy people,
and use it to make those
people even more wealthy.
That's pretty much all it is.
Frankly no one would even
mind if I were to just vanish.
But people who wanted bread
would definitely mind
if their bakery was gone.
Yet for some reason, my job,
which exists completely outside
of that natural human cycle,
pays better money.
When you think
about it logically,
it really doesn't
make any sense at all.
Are you bragging?
No, I'm not.
(cursed fly-buzzing laugh)
(laugh)
Sorry. That was a bit
complicated for me to follow!
Could you take a
step forward, please?
Uhh.
Hm?
How does your shoulder feel now?
Huh?
Oh! Wow, it's lighter!
It's all better!
If it still feels off you
should go see a doctor.
Goodbye.
Ahh!
Oh, uh wait!
Hold on!
Mister?
Hey, thank you!
I hope we see you again soon!
Thank you...
[Bakery Girl] Hey!
Did you hear me?
Thanks, and please
come back again soon!
[Nanami] I always thought I
was a person with no concept
of a "reason for living."
Hello, it's Nanami.
I need to talk to you.
Yes, I want to stop by
Jujutsu Tech tomorrow.
Why are you laughing?
Idle Transfiguration.
I'm so grateful to you.
Save your gratitude.
I've already received more
than enough of that from others.
I've no regrets.
(snickers)
(glass breaks)
(surprised gasps)
(short attack roar)
How was he able to get in?
That's it.
The more resistant the
inside of the barrier is,
the weaker it is to
attacks from outside.
Domains are barriers meant
for trapping something inside,
so they're actually
easy to invade,
because there's no
merit in doing so.
That's even more true with
Domains like Infinite Void
and Self-Embodiment
of Perfection,
which guarantee victory once
they've ensnared their target.
However, inside Itadori,
there lies something
that must not be touched!
I warned you,
there'd be no second time.
(shock gasps)
[Nanami] There is
no one in this world
more proud and conceited.
He lives guided by only his
own pleasure and displeasure.
Whether you die or you
die doesn't matter to me.
Aside from him.
I truly don't care.
(pain moan)
"JUJUTSU KAISEN"
What just happened?
(determined grunt)
(charge yell)
I'll kill you!
Domain Expansion really
burns cursed energy.
It truly is a trump
card, a final technique.
And that damn Sukuna just...
But this is the critical moment!
Squeeze it out!
The last of my cursed energy!
(monster roar)
The target's huge.
The flow of cursed
energy is calm.
There are no options.
I know I can land my attack.
This is my last chance!
I don't need any more tactics!
Divergent Fist!
Huh?
Huh!
What's this lack of feedback?
Bye-bye!
Hold it!
This was fun!
Shit.
Ino!
The core has escaped
back into the sewers.
Yeah.
Please scour everything
from my current
location to the southeast.
Even you could
exorcise him right now.
We need to go after him and...
Huh?
Itadori!
Come on body, move!
You're going to kill
that thing, aren't you?
You said you were gonna
-crush him into a pulp!
-Itadori!
Itadori!
(groan into panting grunt)
(giggling)
So that was the King of
Curses, Ryoumen Sukuna.
He should have less total
cursed energy than Jougo
at this point in
time, and yet...
That presence!
His soul's on a different level.
I'm certain of it.
Even if we're all wiped out,
as long as Sukuna
is resurrected,
the age of curses will come.
But damn, this still sucks.
Right now, I want nothing
more than to kill Yuuji Itadori!
Arrgghh, it's so frustrating!
But whatever, because,
unlike his body I can
keep killing his soul
over and over again.
So next time what would
be a fun way to kill it?
(malicious giggle)
[Nanami] You were
told to rest, weren't you?
[Itadori] Is this my lecture?
I have no lecture
at all to give you.
You're the one
who saved my life.
I saved you?
That patchwork's
cursed technique
is interfering with the soul.
Because you invaded
his Expansion Domain,
he wound up inadvertently
touching Sukuna's soul.
I was saved because of that.
But, I never swapped
out with Sukuna.
[Nanami] Sukuna never came out.
Our opponent went in.
Then it wasn't me who saved you.
It was just Sukuna's whim.
Nanami, I killed a person today.
People die.
There's no stopping that.
So I wanted them to at
least have proper deaths.
That's what I thought.
So I was always thinking about
how I could keep that
trigger from being pulled.
But, after pulling
that trigger myself,
I don't understand anymore!
What is a proper death?
I don't know
what that is, either.
Even if all good people
properly died in peace,
and all evil people
were punished in death,
the problem would be that
most people in this world
are neither all
good nor all evil.
Death is the final
destination for all of us,
but no one dies the same death.
Guiding all of them
to their proper end
would be quite arduous.
I personally wouldn't
recommend it.
I know you won't listen.
You'll still try won't you?
I hope you don't get
killed in the process.
And, just as I would've died
today if you hadn't been there,
you'll see that there are plenty
of other people yet to come
who are going to need you too.
Just remember, Itadori,
you're a jujutsu sorcerer now.
(overwhelmed breath)
The survey is
completely anonymous
so please don't
write your names.
When you're done
put them in this box.
"Survey on Bullying"
(mellow instrumental music)
It was you wasn't it, Itou?
You gave Yoshino
the scars, right?
(sneering)
That's rich, coming
from the so-called teacher
who was too scared to do
anything about it at the time.
Anyway he quit school
and moved away, didn't he?
So who cares?
'N what about me?
I've barely been able to move
my left arm since that day!
All we're concerned with
here and now are your crimes.
Use your own time to reflect
on the punishment
you brought on yourself.
And where's your punishment?
Mine is yet to come.
First I have to look at the
things to which I was blind.
Both you, and I,
will have to live with the
crime of killing Yoshino's heart
for the rest of our lives.
I'll be watching you, Itou.
♪ But I'll survive ♪
I don't really understand
what a proper death is.
So for now,
until I do understand,
until I kill him,
I will not
lose again.
(ending theme music
[In Unison] Juju Stroll!
[Toge] Tuna.
Is it ready yet?
Salmon, salmon.
Huh?
These are some
really good meatballs.
So who made 'em?
Oh, I did.
They're easy to make.
"Put all the ingredients in.
Use twice as much ginger."
"Mix together
well and knead it."
"Shape with spoons
and toss into the pot."
"Ingredients"
"Ground chicken, finely
chopped green onions,
"ginger paste, egg
yolks, salt and pepper"
Bonito flakes.
[Nobara] So you like to
cook for yourself, huh?
Not too surprising, actually.
Well, Itadori taught
me how to make 'em.
(Panda chewing)
That's sad.
Itadori's legacy is a meatball.
[Maki] I don't
think that's right.
(sneezing)
These are some
really good meatballs.
Yeah, and guess what,
they're super easy to make.
Even Fushiguro can do it.
I taught him how.
I can't wait to see
those two again.
(upbeat electronic music)
"Episode 14: Kyoto Sister
School Exchange Event
"- Group Battle"